{
    "id": "5dd09bbe24584663b12b1aa32417c12d",
    "title": "Less And Fewer",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "We did …………………. work today than yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "less",
                "fewer"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "29794f244d0c4db7b8ece69c42159b46"
        },
        {
            "question": "He earns ………………….. than his wife.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "less",
                "fewer"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c9cba59439cc4c80a76c21ed9194193b"
        },
        {
            "question": "You should learn to spend ………………….. money on stupid things.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "less",
                "fewer"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "39f68bbd183a4d64b8eadbcfdfac3a4a"
        },
        {
            "question": "You should spend …………………. time on the first task than on the second.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "less",
                "fewer"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "614b94df636e461d84a7c03794700c3d"
        },
        {
            "question": "I answered ………………… questions than you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "fewer",
                "less"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "68e37566f69648ea965fd8bb1a084c06"
        },
        {
            "question": "The job was ………………….. difficult than I expected.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "less",
                "fewer"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "45758fbf8e894c828696a7acf037caf7"
        },
        {
            "question": "I got …………………. blackberries than her.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "fewer",
                "less"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "94125bb3072743bb9c12f48f509ca466"
        },
        {
            "question": "Try to make ………………….. mistakes when you write.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "less",
                "fewer"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ce217284381c4e2d8a7167345b1d3ece"
        },
        {
            "question": "His latest book is …………………. interesting than his last one.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "less",
                "fewer"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "908a90f72bfe49ecb1750dc3a96aa27d"
        },
        {
            "question": "I would buy that car if it were …………………. expensive.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "less",
                "fewer"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9a81d69a79f44020a55e0ea4c7607db6"
        }
    ]
}